<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Foodie</string>

    <string name="Patty">

        \nPs: \nWhile heating oil make sure it does not overheat. \n\nIn the following recipes,
        beef patties are well done cooked. For a juicier patty, cook a medium rare one.

    </string>
    <string name="big_mac">

        Ingredients: \n\n1 brioche bun \n180 grams ground beef 80% lean and 20% fat \n2 cheddar processed cheese slices \n1
        handful of shredded iceberg lettuce \n3 rounded pickle slices \n1 teaspoon diced onions \n2 tablespoons mayo \n2 teaspoons
        ketchup \n1 teaspoon mustard \n2 teaspoons finely diced dill pickles \n1/2 teaspoon sweet paprika \n1/2 teaspoon onion
        powder \n1/2 teaspoon garlic powder \n1 teaspoon white vinegar \n\nInstructions: \n\nStep 1: \n\nSauce: In a bowl, mix
        mayo, ketchup, mustard, diced pickles, sweet paprika, onion powder, garlic powder, and white vinegar. \n\nStep 2: \n\nHeat
        a pan. Cut the bun into 3 parts. First cut in half then cut the top part into 2 equal parts. Lay the cut side down in the
        pan (lay the middle part on both sides) and cook until lightly toasted, 30 seconds to 1 minute. \n\nStep 3: \n\nMake 2
        meat balls 90 grams each and shape the patties. Add oil to the pan and heat well. Cook patties, turning once with
        seasoning each side with salt and black pepper, until browned on both sides and no longer pink inside, 7 to 8 minutes
        total. Remove from pan. \n\nStep 4: \n\nSpread sauce on bottom bun. Add 1/2 teaspoon of diced onions, some shredded
        iceberg, cheese slice, patty, middle part of the bun, spread sauce on its top, the remaining diced onions, pickle
        slices, some shredded iceberg, second cheese slice, and finally the second patty. Spread sauce on top bun and set in
        place.

    </string>

    <string name="cheeseburger">

        Ingredients: \n\n1 brioche bun \n140 grams ground beef 80% lean and 20% fat \n2 cheddar processed cheese slices \n1
        tablespoon ketchup \n3/4 tablespoon mayo \n1/4 tablespoon mustard \n1/4 teaspoon hot sauce (optional) \n1/2 teaspoon
        onion powder \n1/2 teaspoon garlic powder \n1/8 teaspoon salt \n\nInstructions: \n\nStep 1: \n\nSauce: In a bowl,
        mix ketchup, mayo, mustard, onion powder, garlic powder, salt, and hot sauce. \n\nStep 2: \n\nHeat a pan. Cut the bun
        and lay the cut side down in the pan and cook until lightly toasted, 30 seconds to 1 minute. \n\nStep 3: \n\nForm 2 meat
        balls 70 grams each. Add oil to the pan and heat well. Lay the meat balls in the pan and smash them. Season the upside of
        the smashed balls with salt and black pepper. Cook until browned, flip and season again the cooked side. Top each patty
        with a cheese slice. After melting, add one patty on the other and remove from pan. \n\nStep 4: \n\nSpread sauce on
        bottom bun. Add the smashed patties. Spread sauce on top bun and set in place.

    </string>

    <string name="cheesy_caramelized">

        Ingredients: \n\n1 brioche bun \n500 -> 700 grams onions \n50 ml olive oil \n2 teaspoons salt \n120 grams ground beef
        80% lean and 20% fat \n2 bacon slices \n1 cheddar processed cheese slice \n1 tablespoon butter \n1 tablespoon
        flour (zero) \n1/4 cup hot milk \n1/8 teaspoon salt \n1/8 teaspoon black pepper \n\nInstructions: \n\nStep
        1: \n\nSlice the onions into wings. Add olive oil to a pan (preferrable a stainless-steel pan) and wait until heated
        well then add the onions. Add 2 teaspoons salt mix and set heat to high. Check on them periodically, whenever the
        onions in the bottom are brown, stir all of them to get white ones to the bottom. Repeat this step to have all onions
        become brown (15-20 min). If onions are becoming black not brown, lower the heat a bit.  Finally set the heat to low
        and cover for 20-30 minutes. Stir every 3 minutes. \n\nStep 2: \n\nHeat a pan, add butter, and wait until it melts then
        add flour and stir well until flour become light brown. Add milk and stir until boiling. Add 1/8 teaspoon salt and 1/8
        teaspoon black pepper. Mix well and leave for10 min on medium heat. \n\nStep 3: \n\nHeat a pan. Cut the bun and lay the
        cut side down in the pan and cook until lightly toasted, 30 seconds to 1 minute. \n\nStep 4: \n\nIn a pan, cook the
        bacon. \n\nStep 5: \n\nMake a meat ball of 120 grams and shape the patty. Add oil to the pan and heat well. Cook patty,
        turning once with seasoning each side with salt and black pepper, until browned on both sides and no longer pink inside,
        7 to 8 minutes total then add cheese slice on top of the patty. Remove from pan. \n\nStep 6: \n\nSpread sauce on the
        bottom bun. Add caramelized onions, patty, bacon and sauce on top. Set bun top in place.

    </string>

    <string name="buttermilk_chicken_burger">

        Ingredients: \n\n1 brioche bun \n3/4 cup milk \n1 lemon \n1 tablespoon salt \n1/4 teaspoon black pepper \n1/4 teaspoon
        onion powder \n1/4 teaspoon garlic powder \n1 chicken breast \n2 tablespoons honey \n1.5 tablespoons butter \n8
        tablespoons flour \n1.5 teaspoon starch \n1 tablespoon mayo \n\nInstructions: \n\nStep 1: \n\nButtermilk: In a bowl,
        squeeze lemon and add milk then mix. Leave for 10 minutes. Add salt, black pepper, onion powder, and garlic powder.
        Cut the chicken breast in half and add both parts to the buttermilk. Leave for minimum 1 hour in fridge after covering
        with cling film (preferably more time). \n\nStep 2: \n\nCut the chicken breast in half and add both parts to the
        buttermilk. Leave for minimum 1 hour in fridge after covering with cling film (preferably more time). \n\nStep
        3: \n\nIn a bowl add flour, pinch of salt, and starch. Mix well. \n\nStep 4: \n\nSauce: In a pan, add honey. Add 1
        teaspoon of water if the honey is thick. Cook on high heat until boiling and a change in color to light brown. Add 1
        tablespoon water, mix quickly to cool the mixture. Add butter until it melts then mix for 30 seconds and turn off the
        heat. Add to a cup to cool down. \n\nStep 5: \n\nHeat a pan. Cut the bun and lay the cut side down in the pan and cook
        until lightly toasted, 30 seconds to 1 minute. \n\nStep 6: \n\nTake out the breast and cover it with flour. Tap excess
        flour out of the breast and return to the buttermilk. Put it back into flour. Ready to fry. \n\nStep 7: \n\nIn a frier,
        add oil and heat well to have hot oil. Add the breast and lower the heat a little. After taking it out, add honey sauce
        all over the fried chicken. \n\nStep 8: \n\nSpread mayo on the bottom bun. Add both fried chicken breasts, shredded
        iceberg, and pickles. Set bun top in place.

    </string>

    <string name="crispy_chicken_burger">

        Ingredients: \n\n1 brioche bun \n2 lettuce leaves \n2 fresh onions - ring shaped \n1 tomato slice \n1/2 cup milk \n1/2
        lemon \n1 tablespoon salt \n1/4 teaspoon black pepper \n1/4 teaspoon onion powder \n1/4 teaspoon garlic powder \n1/8
        teaspoon cumin \n1/8 teaspoon cinnamon \n1/8 teaspoon curry \n1/4 teaspoon paprika \n1/2 chicken breast \n5 tablespoons
        flour \n1 teaspoon starch \n1 tablespoon ketchup \n1/4 tablespoon mayo \n1/4 tablespoon mustard \n1/4 teaspoon hot sauce
        (optional) \n1/2 teaspoon onion powder \n1/2 teaspoon garlic powder \n1/4 teaspoon salt \n\nInstructions: \n\nStep 1: \n\nButtermilk:
        In a bowl, squeeze lemon and milk. Leave for 10 minutes. Add salt, black pepper, onion powder, garlic powder, cumin,
        cinnamon, paprika, and curry. \n\nStep 2: \n\nAdd the chicken breast to the buttermilk. Leave for minimum 1 hour in
        fridge after covering with cling film (preferably more time). \n\nStep 3: \n\nIn a bowl, mix ketchup, mayo, mustard,
        onion powder, garlic powder, salt, and hot sauce. \n\nStep 4: \n\nIn a bowl add flour, pinch of salt, and starch.
        Mix well. \n\nStep 5: \n\nHeat a pan. Cut the bun and lay the cut side down in the pan and cook until lightly toasted,
        30 seconds to 1 minute. \n\nStep 6: \n\nTake out the breast and cover it with flour. Tap excess flour out of the breast
        and return to the buttermilk. Put it back into flour. Ready to fry. \n\nStep 7: \n\nIn a frier, add oil and heat well to
        have hot oil. Add the breast and lower the heat a little. Remove when fried well. \n\nStep 8: \n\nSpread sauce on the bottom
        bun. Add lettuce leaf, onion, chicken breast, tomato, onion, and lettuce. Spread sauce on top bun and set in place.

    </string>

    <string name="pizza_burger">

        Ingredients: \n\n1 brioche bun \nPizza sauce \n1 teaspoon olive oil \n100 grams ground sausage \n80 grams
        mozzarella \nPepperoni 3-4 slices \n\nInstructions: \n\nStep 1: \n\nHeat a pan. Cut the bun and lay the cut side
        down in the pan and cook until lightly toasted, 30 seconds to 1 minute. \n\nStep 2: \n\nAdd oil to a pan and cook
        sausages. \n\nStep 3: \n\nSpread pizza sauce on bottom bun. Add sausage, cheese, and pepperoni. Put in the
        microwave. Spread pizza sauce on top bun and set in place.

    </string>

</resources>